In this video I am telling my loved ones about filling the new motor PM
ISA number, it is
very small and
given in a very easy shortcut,
you can fill it easily, to fill it
here you have also been given toll free number
100,
1800, 103,
2292, this is for those customers who have got their vehicles
manufactured from India,
for them because the Indian
add WhatsApp has merged, okay, so it is
for them, so this motor game can be downloaded
by going to my description box on you, you
can also download it from the truck,
you will download it easily and after
downloading it you can fill it, it is very easy,
first of all if you have to select, then
click on the toll free number, you have
done it on the toll free number, before clicking on it
you should have RC insurance, it is okay and
keep the DL with you, they will ask for the utility, after that
your Prem gadget will be there, so when Prem is registered,
note down the second number,
after registering those numbers,
keep that 18 number and if you want to make any correction in it, first of all you have to
give the policy number  And enter the number five, its
number is visible, enter the previous number
brother, whatever your brother's number is,
like Chhattisgarh has it, then
CG-04 ABCD 12345 Dadhi yes number last
of
Pandhurna, you can enter the number here
2 3 4 5 6 7 whatever it is, engine number,
put the last five or six digits 3 4 5 6 7, okay,
after that see here these free mode
chakli minute inch and that means, whatever
vehicle you are planning and in which
policy in lemon juice, according to the policy,
you have to enter the name in it, whatever will be the
call center name in the policy, you have to enter it here,
enter its address here,
whatever is the city pin code, state, you will
enter the mobile numbers here, okay,
you are called from the replay mobile number, now
use mobile number 6 on this number, you have to
enter the mobile number, it is active, you should not
call the body weekly, enter its mail ID here,
in which character you will get Ladli's this
my degree, in that you will get more  Confirmation comes
that you have a compass, this film may not be passed
or it is a cream hold to, whatever it is, after that
now see the loss details, hide the details, delete them, when the
accident happened, you have to fill that, you have to
fill that period and at what time you have to
fill it here, please enter the name of the place of accident,
whatever is there, you have to enter it,
how the accident happened, okay, suppose you were
going somewhere and while driving the
car hits the divider, you take this auspicious day, there is no
problem, after that the
details of the driver, the time of accident, at
which time he was driving,
enter his name, enter his age,
what did he do when my payment came, enter the
driving dress number, till
when is the driving license held and the weighing machine
and also such VLC which you send, Noida
Authority driving is written in it,
whatever is made, from which district it is made, for example,
suppose CG-04, then it will be Raipur,
if your driving is
written CG-04 in it, then enter this type,
it is written zero six, then what will happen, it will be
monsoon, okay  Enter it in this way,
if you are a Back Back Birla driver, if
you are a driver with text 9483, then
send the text and
enter the relation with the driver, the owner is your mother Resham's, enter it,
if you are not the owner,
enter the pen drive paste, if that is also
not there, then enter the relative's name here,
details of the police report in the box, if
any third person has an accident in your vehicle,
hand or leg fracture, then file an FIR,
launch the FIR, press it here, if you do
not want to, then note down the FIR
number and enter the police station, it is
okay, the front part is immediate,
enter what is in the property,
its commercial vehicle
permit number has to be entered, till when is the permit read, till
when is the fitness plate, its permit
number, passenger song, if it is a passenger bus, then how many
passengers were sitting in it, how much money, definitely, what happened, who got
injured, you have to write about it,
Chappadchidi Malwa, so the
daughter Aathiya was going to the next of the goods, it is
necessary to give the bill, okay, after that if
I have the information with you, you have to submit the RC, the
photocopy of the driving license is absolutely
clear, this is the deposit  If you take out a photo of the gold
by WhatsApping it, it is appearing black,
otherwise it gets rejected, file an FIR, if it is
ready then it is fine and if
this food of the fire brigade has been done then what is your daily time, still it
increases then its
report has to be entered here, fitness
certificate ok and the name of your bank, Central Bank, the
bank, branch code, city
magistrate, IFSC code, MICR code, pay
account in the same account, in the name of which
spring you have to lift from the shampoo, otherwise if it is
wrong then there will be problem, ok,
enter the name, enter the record number,
UP Idea, if this is the address above then ok, you
need it first,
enter the search place of the day on which you made the claim,
sign here ok and after signing,
cooperate with all the topic committee,
give it a hard copy so that the film can be processed,
how was the video, if you liked the video then
please like,
subscribe to our channel and share,
if you have any problem,
ask me by commenting, I will help you,
thank you.